starmusiq.xyz 2017-11-29

# Privacy Policy For Starmusiq.xyz

**Privacy Policy For[Starmusiq.xyz](http://starmusiq.xyz/)**

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which starmusiq.info collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the https://starmusiq.la website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by starmusiq.info  
**Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on Starmusiq.xyz. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

**Contacting us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:  
starmusiq.xyz  
info[at]starmusiq.xyz

This document was last updated on June 06, 2017
